Marvin Leath papers, Inclusive: 1954-1994, undated; Bulk: 1979-1991
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
- Correspondence, 1978-1990, undated; 3
  - General, 1981-1990; 1
    - May (9 of 13), 1985 (Box 156, Folder 4)
    - May (10 of 13), 1985 (Box 156, Folder 5)
    - May (11 of 13), 1985 (Box 156, Folder 6)
    - May (12 of 13), 1985 (Box 157, Folder 1)
    - May (13 of 13), 1985 (Box 157, Folder 2)
    - June (1 of 11), 1985 (Box 157, Folder 3)
    - June (2 of 11), 1985 (Box 157, Folder 4)
    - June (3 of 11), 1985 (Box 157, Folder 5)
    - June (4 of 11), 1985 (Box 157, Folder 6)
    - June (5 of 11), 1985 (Box 158, Folder 1)
    - June (6 of 11), 1985 (Box 158, Folder 2)
    - June (7 of 11), 1985 (Box 158, Folder 3)
    - June (8 of 11), 1985 (Box 158, Folder 4)
    - June (9 of 11), 1985 (Box 158, Folder 5)
    - June (10 of 11), 1985 (Box 158, Folder 6)
    - June (11 of 11), 1985 (Box 159, Folder 1)
    - July (1 of 11), 1985 (Box 159, Folder 2)
    - July (2 of 11), 1985 (Box 159, Folder 3)
    - July (3 of 11), 1985 (Box 159, Folder 4)
    - July (4 of 11), 1985 (Box 159, Folder 5)
    - July (5 of 11), 1985 (Box 159, Folder 6)
    - July (6 of 11), 1985 (Box 159, Folder 7)
    - July (7 of 11), 1985 (Box 160, Folder 1)
    - July (8 of 11), 1985 (Box 160, Folder 2)
    - July (9 of 11), 1985 (Box 160, Folder 3)
    - July (10 of 11), 1985 (Box 160, Folder 4)
    - July (11 of 11), 1985 (Box 160, Folder 5)
    - August (1 of 8), 1985 (Box 160, Folder 6)
    - August (2 of 8), 1985 (Box 161, Folder 1)
    - August (3 of 8), 1985 (Box 161, Folder 2)
    - August (4 of 8), 1985 (Box 161, Folder 3)
    - August (5 of 8), 1985 (Box 161, Folder 4)
    - August (6 of 8), 1985 (Box 161, Folder 5)
    - August (7 of 8), 1985 (Box 161, Folder 6)
    - August (8 of 8), 1985 (Box 162, Folder 1)
    - September (1 of 8), 1985 (Box 162, Folder 2)
    - September (2 of 8), 1985 (Box 162, Folder 3)
    - September (3 of 8), 1985 (Box 162, Folder 4)
    - September (3 of 8), 1985 (Box 162, Folder 5)
    - September (4 of 8), 1985 (Box 162, Folder 6)
    - September (5 of 8), 1985 (Box 162, Folder 7)
    - September (6 of 8), 1985 (Box 163, Folder 1)
    - September (7 of 8), 1985 (Box 163, Folder 2)
    - September (8 of 8), 1985 (Box 163, Folder 3)
    - October (1 of 13), 1985 (Box 163, Folder 4)
    - October (2 of 13), 1985 (Box 163, Folder 5)
    - October (3 of 13), 1985 (Box 163, Folder 6)
    - October (4 of 13), 1985 (Box 164, Folder 1)
    - October (5 of 13), 1985 (Box 164, Folder 2)
    - October (6 of 13), 1985 (Box 164, Folder 3)
    - October (7 of 13), 1985 (Box 164, Folder 4)
    - October (8 of 13), 1985 (Box 164, Folder 5)
    - October (9 of 13), 1985 (Box 165, Folder 1)
    - October (10 of 13), 1985 (Box 165, Folder 2)
    - October (11 of 13), 1985 (Box 165, Folder 3)
    - October (12 of 13), 1985 (Box 165, Folder 4)
    - October (13 of 13), 1985 (Box 165, Folder 5)
    - November (1 of 10), 1985 (Box 166, Folder 1)
    - November (2 of 10), 1985 (Box 166, Folder 2)
    - November (3 of 10), 1985 (Box 166, Folder 3)
    - November (4 of 10), 1985 (Box 166, Folder 4)
    - November (5 of 10), 1985 (Box 166, Folder 5)
    - November (6 of 10), 1985 (Box 167, Folder 1)
    - November (7 of 10), 1985 (Box 167, Folder 2)
    - November (8 of 10), 1985 (Box 167, Folder 3)
    - November (9 of 10), 1985 (Box 167, Folder 4)
    - November (10 of 10), 1985 (Box 167, Folder 5)
    - December (1 of 8), 1985 (Box 168, Folder 1)
    - December (2 of 8), 1985 (Box 168, Folder 2)
    - December (3 of 8), 1985 (Box 168, Folder 3)
    - December (4 of 8), 1985 (Box 168, Folder 4)
    - December (5 of 8), 1985 (Box 168, Folder 5)
    - December (6 of 8), 1985 (Box 169, Folder 1)
    - December (7 of 8), 1985 (Box 169, Folder 2)
    - December (8 of 8), 1985 (Box 169, Folder 3)
    - undated (1 of 2), 1986 (Box 169, Folder 4)
    - undated (2 of 2), 1986 (Box 170, Folder 1)
    - January (1 of 12), 1986 (Box 170, Folder 2)
    - January (2 of 12), 1986 (Box 170, Folder 3)
    - January (3 of 12), 1986 (Box 170, Folder 4)
    - January (4 of 12), 1986 (Box 170, Folder 5)
    - January (5 of 12), 1986 (Box 170, Folder 6)
    - January (6 of 12), 1986 (Box 170, Folder 7)
    - January (7 of 12), 1986 (Box 171, Folder 1)
    - January (8 of 12), 1986 (Box 171, Folder 2)
    - January (9 of 12), 1986 (Box 171, Folder 3)
    - January (10 of 12), 1986 (Box 171, Folder 4)
    - January (11 of 12), 1986 (Box 171, Folder 5)
    - January (12 of 12), 1986 (Box 171, Folder 6)
    - February (1 of 9), 1986 (Box 172, Folder 1)
    - February (2 of 9), 1986 (Box 172, Folder 2)
    - February (3 of 9), 1986 (Box 172, Folder 3)
    - February (4 of 9), 1986 (Box 172, Folder 4)
    - February (5 of 9), 1986 (Box 172, Folder 5)
    - February (6 of 9), 1986 (Box 172, Folder 6)
    - February (7 of 9), 1986 (Box 173, Folder 1)
    - February (8 of 9), 1986 (Box 173, Folder 2)
    - February (9 of 9), 1986 (Box 173, Folder 3)
    - March (1 of 12), 1986 (Box 173, Folder 4)
    - March (2 of 12), 1986 (Box 173, Folder 5)
    - March (3 of 12), 1986 (Box 174, Folder 1)
    - March (4 of 12), 1986 (Box 174, Folder 2)
    - March (5 of 12), 1986 (Box 174, Folder 3)
    - March (6 of 12), 1986 (Box 174, Folder 4)
    - March (7 of 12), 1986 (Box 174, Folder 5)
    - March (8 of 12), 1986 (Box 174, Folder 6)
    - March (9 of 12), 1986 (Box 175, Folder 1)
    - March (10 of 12), 1986 (Box 175, Folder 2)
    - March (11 of 12), 1986 (Box 175, Folder 3)
    - March (12 of 12), 1986 (Box 175, Folder 4)
    - April (1 of 11), 1986 (Box 175, Folder 5)
    - April (2 of 11), 1986 (Box 175, Folder 6)
    - April (3 of 11), 1986 (Box 176, Folder 1)
    - April (4 of 11), 1986 (Box 176, Folder 2)
    - April (5 of 11), 1986 (Box 176, Folder 3)
    - April (6 of 11), 1986 (Box 176, Folder 4)
    - April (7 of 11), 1986 (Box 176, Folder 5)
    - April (8 of 11), 1986 (Box 176, Folder 6)
    - April (9 of 11), 1986 (Box 177, Folder 1)
    - April (10 of 11), 1986 (Box 177, Folder 2)
    - April (11 of 11), 1986 (Box 177, Folder 3)
    - May (1 of 6), 1986 (Box 177, Folder 4)
    - May (2 of 6), 1986 (Box 177, Folder 5)
    - May (3 of 6), 1986 (Box 177, Folder 6)
    - May (4 of 6), 1986 (Box 178, Folder 1)
    - May (5 of 6), 1986 (Box 178, Folder 2)
    - May (6 of 6), 1986 (Box 178, Folder 3)
    - June (1 of 11), 1986 (Box 178, Folder 4)
    - June (2 of 11), 1986 (Box 178, Folder 5)
    - June (3 of 11), 1986 (Box 178, Folder 6)
    - June (4 of 11), 1986 (Box 179, Folder 1)
    - June (5 of 11), 1986 (Box 179, Folder 2)
    - June (6 of 11), 1986 (Box 179, Folder 3)
    - June (7 of 11), 1986 (Box 179, Folder 4)
    - June (8 of 11), 1986 (Box 179, Folder 5)
    - June (9 of 11), 1986 (Box 179, Folder 6)
    - June (10 of 11), 1986 (Box 180, Folder 1)
    - June (11 of 11), 1986 (Box 180, Folder 2)
    - July (1 of 6), 1986 (Box 180, Folder 3)
    - July (2 of 6), 1986 (Box 180, Folder 4)
    - July (3 of 6), 1986 (Box 180, Folder 5)
    - July (4 of 6), 1986 (Box 180, Folder 6)
    - July (5 of 6), 1986 (Box 181, Folder 1)
    - July (6 of 6), 1986 (Box 181, Folder 2)
    - August (1 of 8), 1986 (Box 181, Folder 3)
    - August (2 of 8), 1986 (Box 181, Folder 4)
    - August (3 of 8), 1986 (Box 181, Folder 5)
    - August (4 of 8), 1986 (Box 181, Folder 6)
    - August (5 of 8), 1986 (Box 182, Folder 1)
    - August (6 of 8), 1986 (Box 182, Folder 2)
    - August (7 of 8), 1986 (Box 182, Folder 3)
    - August (8 of 8), 1986 (Box 182, Folder 4)
    - September (1 of 8), 1986 (Box 182, Folder 5)
    - September (2 of 8), 1986 (Box 182, Folder 6)
    - September (3 of 8), 1986 (Box 183, Folder 1)
    - September (4 of 8), 1986 (Box 183, Folder 2)
    - September (5 of 8), 1986 (Box 183, Folder 3)
    - September (6 of 8), 1986 (Box 183, Folder 4)
    - September (7 of 8), 1986 (Box 183, Folder 5)
    - September (8 of 8), 1986 (Box 184, Folder 1)
    - October (1 of 10), 1986 (Box 184, Folder 2)
    - October (2 of 10), 1986 (Box 184, Folder 3)
    - October (3 of 10), 1986 (Box 184, Folder 4)
    - October (4 of 10), 1986 (Box 184, Folder 5)
    - October (5 of 10), 1986 (Box 184, Folder 6)
    - October (6 of 10), 1986 (Box 184, Folder 7)
    - October (7 of 10), 1986 (Box 185, Folder 1)
    - October (8 of 10), 1986 (Box 185, Folder 2)
    - October (9 of 10), 1986 (Box 185, Folder 3)
    - October (10 of 10), 1986 (Box 185, Folder 4)
    - November (1 of 5), 1986 (Box 185, Folder 5)
    - November (2 of 5), 1986 (Box 185, Folder 6)
    - November (3 of 5), 1986 (Box 186, Folder 1)
    - November (4 of 5), 1986 (Box 186, Folder 2)
    - November (5 of 5), 1986 (Box 186, Folder 3)
    - December (1 of 8), 1986 (Box 186, Folder 4)
    - December (2 of 8), 1986 (Box 186, Folder 5)
    - December (3 of 8), 1986 (Box 186, Folder 6)
    - December (4 of 8), 1986 (Box 186, Folder 7)
    - December (5 of 8), 1986 (Box 187, Folder 1)
    - December (6 of 8), 1986 (Box 187, Folder 2)
    - December (7 of 8), 1986 (Box 187, Folder 3)
    - December (8 of 8), 1986 (Box 187, Folder 5)
    - January (1 of 8), 1987 (Box 187, Folder 6)
    - January (2 of 8), 1987 (Box 187, Folder 7)
    - January (3 of 8), 1987 (Box 188, Folder 1)
    - January (4 of 8), 1987 (Box 188, Folder 2)
    - January (5 of 8), 1987 (Box 188, Folder 3)
    - January (6 of 8), 1987 (Box 188, Folder 4)
    - January (7 of 8), 1987 (Box 188, Folder 5)
    - January (8 of 8), 1987 (Box 189, Folder 1)
    - February (1 of 15), 1987 (Box 189, Folder 2)
    - February (2 of 15), 1987 (Box 189, Folder 3)
    - February (3 of 15), 1987 (Box 189, Folder 4)
    - February (4 of 15), 1987 (Box 189, Folder 5)
    - February (5 of 15), 1987 (Box 189, Folder 6)
    - February (6 of 15), 1987 (Box 190, Folder 1)
    - February (7 of 15), 1987 (Box 190, Folder 2)
    - February (8 of 15), 1987 (Box 190, Folder 3)
    - February (9 of 15), 1987 (Box 190, Folder 4)
    - February (10 of 15), 1987 (Box 190, Folder 5)
    - February (11 of 15), 1987 (Box 190, Folder 6)
    - February (12 of 15), 1987 (Box 191, Folder 1)
    - February (13 of 15), 1987 (Box 191, Folder 2)
    - February (14 of 15), 1987 (Box 191, Folder 3)
    - February (15 of 15), 1987 (Box 191, Folder 4)
    - March (1 of 10), 1987 (Box 191, Folder 5)
    - March (2 of 10), 1987 (Box 191, Folder 6)
    - March (3 of 10), 1987 (Box 192, Folder 1)
    - March (4 of 10), 1987 (Box 192, Folder 2)
    - March (5 of 10), 1987 (Box 192, Folder 3)
    - March (6 of 10), 1987 (Box 192, Folder 4)
    - March (7 of 10), 1987 (Box 192, Folder 5)
    - March (8 of 10), 1987 (Box 192, Folder 6)
    - March (9 of 10), 1987 (Box 193, Folder 1)
    - March (10 of 10), 1987 (Box 193, Folder 2)
    - April (1 of 6), 1987 (Box 193, Folder 3)
    - April (2 of 6), 1987 (Box 193, Folder 4)
    - April (3 of 6), 1987 (Box 193, Folder 5)
    - April (4 of 6), 1987 (Box 193, Folder 6)
    - April (5 of 6), 1987 (Box 194, Folder 1)
    - April (6 of 6), 1987 (Box 194, Folder 2)
    - May (1 of 8), 1987 (Box 194, Folder 3)
    - May (2 of 8), 1987 (Box 194, Folder 4)
    - May (3 of 8), 1987 (Box 194, Folder 5)
    - May (4 of 8), 1987 (Box 194, Folder 6)
    - May (5 of 8), 1987 (Box 195, Folder 1)
    - May (6 of 8), 1987 (Box 195, Folder 2)
    - May (7 of 8), 1987 (Box 195, Folder 3)
    - May (8 of 8), 1987 (Box 195, Folder 4)
    - June (1 of 8), 1987 (Box 195, Folder 5)
    - June (2 of 8), 1987 (Box 195, Folder 6)
    - June (3 of 8), 1987 (Box 196, Folder 1)
    - June (4 of 8), 1987 (Box 196, Folder 2)
    - June (5 of 8), 1987 (Box 196, Folder 3)
    - June (6 of 8), 1987 (Box 196, Folder 4)
    - June (7 of 8), 1987 (Box 196, Folder 5)
    - June (8 of 8), 1987 (Box 197, Folder 1)
    - July (1 of 8), 1987 (Box 197, Folder 2)
    - July (2 of 8), 1987 (Box 197, Folder 3)
    - July (3 of 8), 1987 (Box 197, Folder 4)
    - July (4 of 8), 1987 (Box 197, Folder 5)
    - July (5 of 8), 1987 (Box 197, Folder 6)
    - July (6 of 8), 1987 (Box 198, Folder 1)
    - July (7 of 8), 1987 (Box 198, Folder 2)
    - July (8 of 8), 1987 (Box 198, Folder 3)
    - August (1 of 7), 1987 (Box 198, Folder 4)
    - August (2 of 7), 1987 (Box 198, Folder 5)
    - August (3 of 7), 1987 (Box 198, Folder 6)
    - August (4 of 7), 1987 (Box 199, Folder 1)
    - August (5 of 7), 1987 (Box 199, Folder 2)
    - August (6 of 7), 1987 (Box 199, Folder 3)
    - August (7 of 7), 1987 (Box 199, Folder 4)
    - September (1 of 10), 1987 (Box 199, Folder 5)
    - September (2 of 10), 1987 (Box 199, Folder 6)
    - September (3 of 10), 1987 (Box 200, Folder 1)
    - September (4 of 10), 1987 (Box 200, Folder 2)
    - September (5 of 10), 1987 (Box 200, Folder 3)
    - September (6 of 10), 1987 (Box 200, Folder 4)
    - September (7 of 10), 1987 (Box 200, Folder 5)
    - September (8 of 10), 1987 (Box 200, Folder 6)
    - September (9 of 10), 1987 (Box 201, Folder 1)
    - September (10 of 10), 1987 (Box 201, Folder 2)
    - October (1 of 9), 1987 (Box 201, Folder 3)
    - October (2 of 9), 1987 (Box 201, Folder 4)
    - October (3 of 9), 1987 (Box 201, Folder 5)
    - October (4 of 9), 1987 (Box 201, Folder 6)
    - October (5 of 9), 1987 (Box 202, Folder 1)
    - October (6 of 9), 1987 (Box 202, Folder 2)
    - October (7 of 9), 1987 (Box 202, Folder 3)
    - October (8 of 9), 1987 (Box 202, Folder 4)
    - October (9 of 9), 1987 (Box 202, Folder 4)
    - November (1 of 8), 1987 (Box 203, Folder 1)
    - November (2 of 8), 1987 (Box 203, Folder 2)
    - November (3 of 8), 1987 (Box 203, Folder 3)
    - November (4 of 8), 1987 (Box 203, Folder 4)
    - November (5 of 8), 1987 (Box 203, Folder 5)
    - November (6 of 8), 1987 (Box 203, Folder 6)
    - November (7 of 8), 1987 (Box 204, Folder 1)
    - November (8 of 8), 1987 (Box 204, Folder 2)
    - December (1 of 5), 1987 (Box 204, Folder 3)
    - December (2 of 5), 1987 (Box 204, Folder 4)
    - December (3 of 5), 1987 (Box 204, Folder 5)
    - December (4 of 5), 1987 (Box 204, Folder 6)
    - December (5 of 5), 1987 (Box 205, Folder 1)
    - January (1 of 8), 1988 (Box 205, Folder 2)
    - January (2 of 8), 1988 (Box 205, Folder 3)
    - January (3 of 8), 1988 (Box 205, Folder 4)
    - January (4 of 8), 1988 (Box 205, Folder 5)
    - January (5 of 8), 1988 (Box 205, Folder 6)
    - January (6 of 8), 1988 (Box 206, Folder 1)
    - January (7 of 8), 1988 (Box 206, Folder 2)
    - January (8 of 8), 1988 (Box 206, Folder 3)
    - February (1 of 8), 1988 (Box 206, Folder 4)
    - February (2 of 8), 1988 (Box 206, Folder 5)
    - February (3 of 8), 1988 (Box 206, Folder 6)
    - February (4 of 8), 1988 (Box 207, Folder 1)
    - February (5 of 8), 1988 (Box 207, Folder 2)
    - February (6 of 8), 1988 (Box 207, Folder 3)
    - February (7 of 8), 1988 (Box 207, Folder 4)
    - February (8 of 8), 1988 (Box 207, Folder 5)
    - March (1 of 12), 1988 (Box 207, Folder 6)
    - March (2 of 12), 1988 (Box 208, Folder 1)
    - March (3 of 12), 1988 (Box 208, Folder 2)
    - March (4 of 12), 1988 (Box 208, Folder 3)
    - March (5 of 12), 1988 (Box 208, Folder 4)
    - March (6 of 12), 1988 (Box 208, Folder 5)
    - March (7 of 12), 1988 (Box 208, Folder 6)
    - March (8 of 12), 1988 (Box 209, Folder 1)
    - March (9 of 12), 1988 (Box 209, Folder 2)
    - March (10 of 12), 1988 (Box 209, Folder 3)
    - March (11 of 12), 1988 (Box 209, Folder 4)
    - March (12 of 12), 1988 (Box 209, Folder 5)
    - April (1 of 10), 1988 (Box 209, Folder 6)
    - April (2 of 10), 1988 (Box 210, Folder 1)
    - April (3 of 10), 1988 (Box 210, Folder 2)
    - April (4 of 10), 1988 (Box 210, Folder 3)
    - April (5 of 10), 1988 (Box 210, Folder 4)
    - April (6 of 10), 1988 (Box 210, Folder 5)
    - April (7 of 10), 1988 (Box 210, Folder 6)
    - April (8 of 10), 1988 (Box 211, Folder 1)
    - April (9 of 10), 1988 (Box 211, Folder 2)
    - April (10 of 10), 1988 (Box 211, Folder 3)
    - May (1 of 8), 1988 (Box 211, Folder 4)
    - May (2 of 8), 1988 (Box 211, Folder 5)
    - May (3 of 8), 1988 (Box 211, Folder 6)
    - May (4 of 8), 1988 (Box 212, Folder 1)
    - May (5 of 8), 1988 (Box 212, Folder 2)
    - May (6 of 8), 1988 (Box 212, Folder 3)
    - May (7 of 8), 1988 (Box 212, Folder 4)
    - May (8 of 8), 1988 (Box 212, Folder 5)
    - June (1 of 7), 1988 (Box 212, Folder 6)
    - June (2 of 7), 1988 (Box 213, Folder 1)
    - June (3 of 7), 1988 (Box 213, Folder 2)
    - June (4 of 7), 1988 (Box 213, Folder 3)
    - June (5 of 7), 1988 (Box 213, Folder 4)
    - June (6 of 7), 1988 (Box 213, Folder 5)
    - June (7 of 7), 1988 (Box 213, Folder 6)
    - July (1 of 7), 1988 (Box 214, Folder 1)
    - July (2 of 7), 1988 (Box 214, Folder 2)
    - July (3 of 7), 1988 (Box 214, Folder 3)
    - July (4 of 7), 1988 (Box 214, Folder 4)
    - July (5 of 7), 1988 (Box 214, Folder 5)
    - July (6 of 7), 1988 (Box 214, Folder 6)
    - July (7 of 7), 1988 (Box 215, Folder 1)
    - August (1 of 6), 1988 (Box 215, Folder 2)
    - August (2 of 6), 1988 (Box 215, Folder 3)
    - August (3 of 6), 1988 (Box 215, Folder 4)
    - August (4 of 6), 1988 (Box 215, Folder 5)
    - August (5 of 6), 1988 (Box 215, Folder 6)
    - August (6 of 6), 1988 (Box 216, Folder 1)
    - September (1 of 4), 1988 (Box 216, Folder 2)
    - September (2 of 4), 1988 (Box 216, Folder 3)
    - September (3 of 4), 1988 (Box 216, Folder 4)
    - September (4 of 4), 1988 (Box 216, Folder 5)
    - October (1 of 4), 1988 (Box 217, Folder 1)
    - October (2 of 4), 1988 (Box 217, Folder 2)
    - October (3 of 4), 1988 (Box 217, Folder 3)
    - October (4 of 4), 1988 (Box 217, Folder 4)
    - November (1 of 2), 1988 (Box 217, Folder 5)
    - November (2 of 2), 1988 (Box 217, Folder 6)
    - December (1 of 3), 1988 (Box 218, Folder 1)
    - December (2 of 3), 1988 (Box 218, Folder 2)
    - December (3 of 3), 1988 (Box 218, Folder 3)
    - January (1 of 5), 1989 (Box 218, Folder 4)
    - January (2 of 5), 1989 (Box 218, Folder 5)
    - January (3 of 5), 1989 (Box 218, Folder 6)
    - January (4 of 5), 1989 (Box 219, Folder 1)
    - January (5 of 5), 1989 (Box 219, Folder 2)
    - April, 1989 (Box 219, Folder 3)
    - May, 1989 (Box 219, Folder 4)
    - June, 1989 (Box 219, Folder 5)
    - July, 1989 (Box 219, Folder 6)
    - August, 1989 (Box 219, Folder 7)
    - September (1 of 3), 1989 (Box 219, Folder 8)
    - September (2 of 3), 1989 (Box 219, Folder 9)
    - September (3 of 3), 1989 (Box 219, Folder 10)
    - October (1 of 6), 1989 (Box 219, Folder 11)
    - October (2 of 6), 1989 (Box 219, Folder 12)
    - October (3 of 6), 1989 (Box 220, Folder 1)
    - October (4 of 6), 1989 (Box 220, Folder 2)
    - October (5 of 6), 1989 (Box 220, Folder 3)
    - October (6 of 6), 1989 (Box 220, Folder 4)
    - November (1 of 7), 1989 (Box 220, Folder 5)
    - November (2 of 7), 1989 (Box 220, Folder 6)
    - November (3 of 7), 1989 (Box 220, Folder 7)
    - November (4 of 7), 1989 (Box 220, Folder 8)
    - November (5 of 7), 1989 (Box 221, Folder 1)
    - November (6 of 7), 1989 (Box 221, Folder 2)
    - November (7 of 7), 1989 (Box 221, Folder 3)
    - December (1 of 4), 1989 (Box 221, Folder 4)
    - December (2 of 4), 1989 (Box 221, Folder 5)
    - December (3 of 4), 1989 (Box 221, Folder 6)
    - December (4 of 4), 1989 (Box 222, Folder 1)
    - January (1 of 4), 1990 (Box 222, Folder 2)
    - January (2 of 4), 1990 (Box 222, Folder 3)
    - January (3 of 4), 1990 (Box 222, Folder 4)
    - January (4 of 4), 1990 (Box 222, Folder 5)
    - February (1 of 4), 1990 (Box 222, Folder 6)
    - February (2 of 4), 1990 (Box 222, Folder 7)
    - February (3 of 4), 1990 (Box 222, Folder 8)
    - February (4 of 4), 1990 (Box 223, Folder 1)
    - March (1 of 6), 1990 (Box 223, Folder 2)
    - March (2 of 6), 1990 (Box 223, Folder 3)
    - March (3 of 6), 1990 (Box 223, Folder 4)
    - March (4 of 6), 1990 (Box 223, Folder 5)
    - March (5 of 6), 1990 (Box 223, Folder 6)
    - March (6 of 6), 1990 (Box 223, Folder 7)
    - April (1 of 5), 1990 (Box 224, Folder 1)
    - April (2 of 5), 1990 (Box 224, Folder 2)
    - April (3 of 5), 1990 (Box 224, Folder 3)
    - April (4 of 5), 1990 (Box 224, Folder 4)
    - April (5 of 5), 1990 (Box 224, Folder 5)
    - May (1 of 7), 1990 (Box 224, Folder 6)
    - May (2 of 7), 1990 (Box 225, Folder 1)
    - May (3 of 7), 1990 (Box 225, Folder 2)
    - May (4 of 7), 1990 (Box 225, Folder 3)
    - May (5 of 7), 1990 (Box 225, Folder 4)
    - May (6 of 7), 1990 (Box 225, Folder 5)
    - May (7 of 7), 1990 (Box 225, Folder 6)
    - June (1 of 8), 1990 (Box 225, Folder 7)
    - June (2 of 8), 1990 (Box 226, Folder 1)
    - June (3 of 8), 1990 (Box 226, Folder 2)
    - June (4 of 8), 1990 (Box 226, Folder 3)
    - June (5 of 8), 1990 (Box 226, Folder 4)
    - June (6 of 8), 1990 (Box 226, Folder 5)
    - June (7 of 8), 1990 (Box 226, Folder 6)
    - June (8 of 8), 1990 (Box 227, Folder 1)
    - July (1 of 7), 1990 (Box 227, Folder 2)
    - July (2 of 7), 1990 (Box 227, Folder 3)
    - July (3 of 7), 1990 (Box 227, Folder 4)
    - July (4 of 7), 1990 (Box 227, Folder 5)
    - July (5 of 7), 1990 (Box 227, Folder 6)
    - July (6 of 7), 1990 (Box 227, Folder 7)
    - July (7 of 7), 1990 (Box 228, Folder 1)
    - August (1 of 5), 1990 (Box 228, Folder 2)
    - August (2 of 5), 1990 (Box 228, Folder 3)
    - August (3 of 5), 1990 (Box 228, Folder 4)
    - August (4 of 5), 1990 (Box 228, Folder 5)
    - August (5 of 5), 1990 (Box 228, Folder 6)
    - September (1 of 3), 1990 (Box 228, Folder 7)
    - September (2 of 3), 1990 (Box 229, Folder 1)
    - September (3 of 3), 1990 (Box 229, Folder 2)
    - October (1 of 4), 1990 (Box 229, Folder 3)
    - October (2 of 4), 1990 (Box 229, Folder 4)
    - October (3 of 4), 1990 (Box 229, Folder 5)
    - October (4 of 4), 1990 (Box 229, Folder 6)
    - November, 1990 (Box 229, Folder 7)
    - Co-signed Letters, 1981 (Box 230, Folder 1)
    - Co-signed Letters, 1982 (Box 230, Folder 2)
    - Co-signed Letters, 1983 (Box 230, Folder 3)
    - Co-signed Letters, 1984 (Box 230, Folder 4)
    - Co-signed Letters, 1985 (Box 230, Folder 5)
    - Co-signed Letters, 1986 (Box 230, Folder 6)
    - Co-signed Letters (1 of 2), 1987 (Box 230, Folder 7)
    - Co-signed Letters (2 of 2), 1987 (Box 230, Folder 8)
    - Co-signed Letters, 1988 (Box 231, Folder 1)
    - Co-signed Letters (1 of 3), 1989 (Box 231, Folder 2)
    - Co-signed Letters (2 of 3), 1989 (Box 231, Folder 3)
    - Co-signed Letters (3 of 3), 1989 (Box 231, Folder 4)
    - Co-signed Letters (1 of 2), 1990 (Box 231, Folder 5)
    - Co-signed Letters (2 of 2), 1990 (Box 231, Folder 6)
  - Incoming, 1978-1979; 2
    - A-B, 1979 (Box 232, Folder 1)
    - C-D, 1979 (Box 232, Folder 2)
    - E-H, 1979 (Box 232, Folder 3)
    - I-M, 1978-1979 (Box 232, Folder 4)
    - N-S, 1979 (Box 232, Folder 5)
    - T-Z, 1979 (Box 232, Folder 6)
    - Temple Junior College, 1979 (Box 232, Folder 7)
  - Outgoing, 1978-1981; 3
    - A, 1978 November-1979 June, undated (Box 233, Folder 1)
    - A, July-December, 1979 (Box 233, Folder 2)
    - B, 1978 November-1979 January, undated (Box 233, Folder 3)
    - B, February-March, 1979 (Box 233, Folder 4)
    - B, April-May, 1979 (Box 233, Folder 5)
    - B, June-July, 1979 (Box 233, Folder 6)
    - B, August-September, 1979 (Box 234, Folder 1)
    - B, October-December, 1979 (Box 234, Folder 2)
    - C, 1978 November-1979 March, undated (Box 234, Folder 3)
    - C, April-June, 1979 (Box 234, Folder 4)
    - C, July-September, 1979 (Box 234, Folder 5)
    - C, October-December, 1979 (Box 234, Folder 6)
    - D, 1978 November-1979 March (Box 235, Folder 1)
    - D, April -July, 1979 (Box 235, Folder 2)
    - D, August-December, 1979 (Box 235, Folder 3)
    - E, 1978 November-1979 April (Box 235, Folder 4)
    - E, May-December, 1979 (Box 235, Folder 5)
    - F, 1978 November-1979 February, undated (Box 235, Folder 6)
    - F, March-July, 1979 (Box 235, Folder 7)